{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622561","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622561","name":"The Paris Cafe","address":"2709 South Fort Street","zipcode":"48217","owner":"Wanda Hayes","licenseNumber":"17059A","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"355","coords":"-83.16047,42.26953","geojson":{"id":"51622561","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.160469159,42.269534168]},"properties":{"name":"The Paris Cafe","owner":"Wanda Hayes","address":"2709 South Fort Street","zipcode":"48217","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"17059A","establishmentid":"51622561","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"355","most_recent_license_date":"25/10/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3393","name":"Arthur's Deli","address":"2709 Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"51623463","name":"Grill Culture","address":"2709 Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"2021","name":"Fort St. Eats d/b/a Johnny Noodle King","address":"2601 Fort W.","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"885","name":"Mark Twain K-8","address":"12800 Visger  Rd.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"51622926","name":"Moore Soul Food","address":"3005 Fort Street S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"781","name":"Ciotti Bar","address":"3133 Fort St S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"4068","name":"Ella Mae's Place","address":"2251 Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"1272","name":"Kemeny Recreation Center","address":"2260 Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"3132","name":"Perfect Cafe","address":"2037  Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"2245","name":"Perfect Beat","address":"1941 Fort St. S.","zipcode":"48217"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"53594","inspectionDate":"2020-03-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Closed - left messag","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45333","inspectionDate":"2019-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"Condiments","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.4119","violationDescription":"Sec. 4119. (1) Except as otherwise provided in subsection (2), a person licensed as a food establishment under this chapter shall keep a copy of the current license or temporary license furnished by the department posted and exposed in a conspicuous place for public inspection. A conspicuous place is the principal place where food business is transacted.  (2) In the case of vending machines, the name and address and telephone number of the current vending machine location operator shall be conspicuously displayed on each vending machine.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food Service License","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not displayed","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"LICENSE","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"40736","inspectionDate":"2017-11-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"5-402.13","violationDescription":"SEWAGE shall be conveyed to the point of disposal through an APPROVED sanitary SEWAGE system or other system, including use of SEWAGE transport vehicles, waste retention tanks, pumps, pipes, hoses, and connections that are constructed, maintained, and operated according to LAW.(P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sewage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not conveyed to point of disposal","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor drain(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"5-501.113","violationDescription":"Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables shall be kept tightly covered, unless they are in continuous use.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S) EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the TRASH CAN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.11","violationDescription":"An outdoor storage surface for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnable's shall be constructed of nonabsorbent material such as concrete or asphalt and shall be SMOOTH, durable, and sloped to drain.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"grease barrel","problemDescription":"Stored over","subProblem":"Dirt/soil","location":"OUTSIDE","subLocation":"At the Grease Dumpster","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store over cement or machine laid asphalt that is sloped to drain."},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Front counter","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2011-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622561"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}